# **Richard Williams**

3665 Margaret Street, Houston, TX 47587 <u>activeemailadd1@mail.com</u> (primary) <u>activeemailadd2@mail.com</u> (secondary) activemobilenum

Financial Advisor with 7+ years of experience delivering financial/investment advisory services to high value clients. Proven success in managing multi-million dollar portfolios, driving profitability, and increasing ROI through skillful strategic planning, consulting, and financial advisory services.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### WELLS FARGO ADVISORS,

Houston, TX

Senior Financial Advisor

August 2020-Present

- Deliver financial advice to clients, proposing strategies to achieve short- and long-term objectives for investments, insurance, business and estate planning with minimal risk
- Develop, review, and optimize investment portfolios for 300+ high value clients with over \$190M
  AUM (Assets Under Management)
- Ensure maximum client satisfaction by providing exceptional and personalized service, enhancing client satisfaction ratings from 88% to 99.9% in less than 6 months
- Work closely with specialists from multiple branches, managing investment portfolios for over 800 clients with over \$25M in assets under care

## SUNTRUST INVESTMENT SERVICES, INC.

New Orleans, LA

Financial Advisor

July 2017-August 2020

- Served as knowledgeable financial advisor to clients, managing an over \$20.75M investment portfolio of 90+ individual and corporate clients
- Devised and applied a new training and accountability program that increased productivity from #10 to #3 in the region in less than 2 year period
- Partnered with cross-functional teams in consulting with clients to provide asset management risk strategy and mitigation, which increased AUM by 50%

#### MAVERICK CAPITAL MANAGEMENT

New Orleans, LA

Financial Advisor

July 2014-August 2017

- Served as the primary point of contact for over 15 clients
- Managed the portfolios of several major clients with over \$8.5M in total assets

# **EDUCATION**

#### LOUISIANA STATE UNIVERSITY

**Baton Rouge, LA** 

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration (concentration: finance), Honors: cum laude (GPA: 3.7/4.0)

May 2014

## ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Proficient in MS Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint) Outlook, MS Project, Salesforce, TFS Project Management
- Fluent in English, Spanish, and French